<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2020-12-15T23:41:36.704+03:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="admin"
        cq:template="/apps/training/templates/content-page-template"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Call of Duty: Modern Warfare"
        sling:resourceType="training/components/structure/content-page">
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2020-12-15T23:41:19.443+03:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="core/wcm/components/image/v2/image"
            alt="Call of Duty: Modern Warfare"
            displayPopupTitle="true"
            fileName="Call of Duty: Modern Warfare.jpg"
            isDecorative="false">
            <file/>
        </image>
        <text
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2020-12-15T23:41:36.701+03:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="core/wcm/components/text/v2/text"
            text="&lt;p>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare is a 2019 first-person shooter video game developed by Infinity Ward and published by Activision. Serving as the sixteenth overall installment in the Call of Duty series, as well as a reboot of the Modern Warfare sub-series, it was released on October 25, 2019, for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The game takes place in a realistic and modern setting. The campaign follows a CIA officer and British SAS forces as they team up with rebels from the fictional country of Urzikstan, combating together against Russian forces who have invaded the country. The game's Special Ops mode features cooperative play missions that follow up the campaign's story. The multiplayer mode supports cross-platform multiplayer and cross-platform progression for the first time in the series. It has been reworked for gameplay to be more tactical and introduces new features, such as a Realism mode that removes the HUD as well as a form of the Ground War mode that now supports 64 players.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Infinity Ward began working on the game soon after the release of their 2016 title Call of Duty: Infinite Warfare. They introduced an entirely new engine for the game, which allows for new performance enhancements such as more detailed environments and ray-tracing capabilities. For the campaign, they took influence from real-life conflicts, such as the Syrian Civil War and terrorist incidents that have occurred in London. For the multiplayer, they scrapped the franchise's traditional season pass and removed loot boxes, enabling them to distribute free post-launch content to the playerbase in the form of &amp;quot;Seasons&amp;quot;.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
            textIsRich="true"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
